bcm.edu 2017-01-28

# Privacy | Baylor College of Medicine | Houston, Texas

## Internet Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

Baylor College of Medicine web sites are intended to provide general educational information about services offered by Baylor and to help users arrange more easily for those services. Information on Baylor web sites is written by faculty and staff affiliated with the College, while other information may be from sources outside of Baylor.

**You assume full responsibility for using the information on BCM web sites, and understand and agree that BCM is not responsible or liable for any claim, loss, or damage resulting from its use by you or any user.** While we try to keep the information on this site as accurate as possible, we disclaim any warranty, express or implied, including warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. Baylor also does not warrant that access to the site will be error free or virus free.

Copyright law protects material on Baylor College of Medicine's web sites. Reprinting or otherwise reproducing any document in whole or in part is prohibited, unless prior written consent is obtained from the copyright owner.

By choosing to use the College's web sites, you acknowledge and agree to the terms of this Disclaimer and our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify these terms and policies and recommend that you review them periodically.

## Health Information

If you are a healthcare consumer who chooses to use the health related information on Baylor College of Medicine web sites, you should not rely on that information as professional medical advice or use it to replace any relationship with your physician or other qualified healthcare professional. Baylor College of Medicine web sites are not an attempt to practice medicine or provide specific medical advice and do not establish a doctor-patient relationship. Health-related information on Baylor College of Medicine web sites should not be used to make a diagnosis or to replace or overrule the advice of a qualified healthcare provider.

Users of BCM web sites should not rely on the information contained in any BCM web site for emergency medical treatment. Users should consult with a qualified healthcare professional for answers to specific health related questions.

Some Baylor College of Medicine web sites may allow you to enter your personal health information. Any personal health information you submit electronically to Baylor College of Medicine web sites is done so voluntarily. Baylor College of Medicine will not use or disclose your personal health information without your written consent or authorization, in accordance with applicable state and federal laws.

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of our customers is important to Baylor College of Medicine. We understand that visitors to sites within the Baylor domain, bcm.edu, need to be in control of their personal information.

Therefore, the following is Baylor College of Medicine's Internet Privacy Policy:

  * Your personal information is not required to visit our site. If you choose not to provide personal information, you can still visit the bcm.edu pages.
  * Access to some areas of our site may require appropriate authorization. In that case, your unique user ID and password is required.
  * Access to some areas of our site may require some of your personal information. In that case, this personal information will only be collected if specifically and voluntarily provided and authorized by you.
  * Baylor College of Medicine may collect personally identifiable information only if specifically and voluntarily provided and authorized by you.
  * Baylor College of Medicine may use third-party services or programs to collect or maintain any voluntary personal information you may choose to provide us.
  * Personally identifying information collected will be used only in connection with bcm.edu, or for such purposes as are described at the point of collection.
  * Some information collected is for statistical purposes only. Baylor College of Medicine performs analyses of user behavior in order to measure customer interest in the various areas of our sites.
  * Baylor College of Medicine will make every reasonable effort to protect the personal information that you share with us as outlined in our Internet Security Policy.
  * You do not need to have cookies* enabled to visit bcm.edu.

If you have questions, send them to [pa-webteam@bcm.edu](mailto:pa-webteam@bcm.edu).

#### *Session Cookies and Persistent Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser, along with a Web page, when you access a Web site. A cookie might track the pages you've visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page. There are two kinds of cookies. A session cookie is a line of text that is stored temporarily in your computer's memory. Because a session cookie is never written to a drive, it is destroyed as soon as you close your browser. A persistent cookie is a more permanent line of text that gets saved by your browser to a file on your hard drive.

Baylor College of Medicine uses cookies to count the number of visitors and to improve the usability of our websites. We have set our software so that your browser will only return cookie information to the domain where the cookie originated (in this case, bcm.edu). No other site can request it. Note: Regardless of the particular uses for cookies on Baylor College of Medicine web sites, we will not share any cookie information with any third parties.

## Baylor College of Medicine's Internet Security Policy:

Baylor College of Medicine takes reasonable efforts to safeguard any voluntary personal information you provide us by using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards based on industry standards and best practices.

While we may use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software in some cases to protect the security of your information during transmission, you should know that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed absolutely secure.

Baylor College of Medicine e-mail functionality does not provide a completely secure and confidential means of communication. You should take any appropriate steps to assure yourself that your communication is protected.

**Baylor College of Medicine will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information.**
